[{"answer": "Tall and quiet.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "And what was he like then?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Absolutely shocked.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "-- African-American president, an amazing thing?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I think both are true.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "No, you're right.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "-- you know, it would have been unthinkable that people talked about each other in this way that they are now, quite openly, in Washington?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "NDERWOOD: Well, you know, I had a conversation with my son when this hit the news.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "What do you make of this, as a parent and as an American?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I still say -- and, you know, there's a conversation about do you wear -- can you wear a hoodie, should you not wear a hoodie.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Has it changed?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "The point is, as I said to my son, you're beautiful.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "But is there a point about a young, black teenager and the hoodie as an emblem of suspicion, of a potential troublemaker?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "You're talking about black-on-black crime?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Sixty-eight.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Did you say 68?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Oh, man, Piers, I'm having the time of my life.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Are you excited by this?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Something's missing.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Hmm?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I think the adultery, the paparazzi, everybody cheering and so many -- including many I've worked with -- don't think they deserve such yelling and screaming.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "What is the most corrupting influence, do you think?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "I'm happy I did it for two reasons.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "How do you feel about being involved in one of the really appalling films ever made?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "He's great.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "How do you go wrong with that?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, people keep asking me now because I did \"Exit to Eden,\" and they're not trying -- well, Garry, \"Exit to Eden,\" bombed.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Would you agree that \"Exit to Eden\" was one of the big turkeys?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I think she has it in it, if you can get her to come and, you know, on the set and everything.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Do you think she has it in her to play somebody like Liz Taylor?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "The best one I ever worked with just for all the reasons is Julie Andrews.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Who's been the greatest movie star that you've seen for whatever reason?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "In a dream movie, I'd put somebody that I have.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "In a dream movie?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Hey, nobody moves.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "I want you to get lost, all right?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "In my country, in my life I saw rough patches.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What do you make of what's going on right now?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Well, first there was gossip, and you have gossip, but every country has gossip.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "What has it done to American society and culture -- the Internet -- do you think?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Health care in these days is a bit of a joke.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Are you laughing now?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Richard and Julia really had great chemistry, and part of it is because they liked each other, they didn't know each other, and they liked each other, and when they were working, they didn't have anything else to do.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "You do hint -- just a hint -- an illusion to a romance between Julia Roberts and Richard Gere?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Well, he wasn't in real life.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "He was like the coolest dude on TV, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "ARSHALL: Well, he's cool now.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Was he never cool?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Truly.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "He really is, isn't he?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "He came into my life when I had -- I moved to the beach.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "When did he come into your life, Christian?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I noticed him as a friend.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "You didn't even notice him?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "He's a man like I've never met before.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "I can take that leap?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Which is fine if it's you, but how does he feel about that?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "There can't be many men who are going to object to having somebody like you, internationally famous, beautiful woman saying it's the best sex she's ever had.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "I think he -- it's a love/hate thing with my big mouth, right?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "It's not exactly the most damning thing ever, is it?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, to never say never.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "What did you learn about yourself on this pretty rocky journey?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I guess about 135.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "What's your fighting weight now?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Well, you've thrown me the curve ball and now I'm going to hit it out of the park.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "To any women watching this who have battled this for decades, perhaps, what is the trick to keeping it off?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I'm joking.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "How much sex are you having?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "There isn't.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "There's no easy route, is there?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "I think that is the correct -- I mean, it's a very, very small number.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Is that the statistic?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Oh, no, there's video.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "There are pictures of you naked in a bathtub?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "It's almost like the classic -- I don't want to say, but it's like the classic ugly duckling story, isn't it?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "It's in the book.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Why do you think that at 18, you ended up so overweight, so unhappy, I would guess as well?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "It's unfortunate, but it's -- we are public figures and we put ourselves out there.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "When you see headlines like that, and millions of people are reading them, what does it do to a woman?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "No, I'm sort of an unfamous famous person.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "He says here you never wined about being famous?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "I actually really liked it.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "Is that as horrific as it seems?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "Well, there's weirdos that you meet in a bar too.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "You must get all sorts of weirdos, don't you?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "It's really hard to meet people.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "See, that is true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "No, appearing on a show like this with your handsome new husband, having the greatest sex of all time.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Oh, what, being at a healthy weight or having success?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "AKE: It was an accomplishment.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "When you finished the book and you did the last words and it all went off, what did you feel?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "I'd say hitting bottom and losing my house when I was 21 years old, and being 260 pounds and in an abusive relationship, that was my low point and that was also a gift, because I was able to learn a very valuable lesson about money and -- you know, because I had lost a ton of money in that bad choice of buying a house at 19 years old.", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Of all the things that you talk about in here, the amazing life that you have had up and down, excluding marriage and the birth of children, what has been the greatest and the worst moment of your life, do you think?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "\"Hair Spray.\"", "docId": "120427pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "If I could relive a moment right now, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 794}]